Several molecules have been found in ancient galaxies.
We are still far away from close encounters of the third kind.
microwave is really starting to shoot.
The mission is approaching.
difficult to take in the past.
In early June, astronomers published the image in Nature Other.
Surrounded by a circle of orange light outside the blue core.
This is a new scale field circle.
This is a portal.
This is the birth ring of alien civilization.
In fact.
This is a five-year-old galaxy with several rings in its direction.
含有有機物多環芳香煙的古老星系
His name is 418.
47 to Sue
because the name is very long.
or discuss.
Click the join button to become on member.